Personal Injury Lawyers Serving the Entire U.S.

Get started by searching below:

Get started by searching below:  Search

[_For legal help call:_ **(800) 995-1212** _Attorney Advertising_](tel:+18009951212 "Click to call (800) 995-1212")

Menu

    [**Have You Or a Loved One Suffered From a Defective Product or Device?**
    
    Get Help Now](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/legal-case-review/ "Have You Or a Loved One Suffered From a Defective Product or Device?")

    [**Have You Or A Loved One Suffered From Nursing Home Abuse?**
    
    Get Help Now](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/nursing-home-abuse/legal-case-review/ "Have You Or A Loved One Suffered From Nursing Home Abuse?")

    [**Get Help After a Mesothelioma Diagnosis**
    
    Get Help Now](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/mesothelioma/legal/legal-case-review/ "Get Help After a Mesothelioma Diagnosis")

[Home](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/ "Home")  /  [Privacy Policy](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/privacy/ "Privacy Policy")

Privacy Policy
==============

About Sokolove Law
------------------

For more than 45 years, Sokolove Law has worked to educate people about their rights, most frequently serving the role as a mesothelioma law firm. We’ve helped people in all 50 states get the legal support they need to move personal injury claims successfully through the court system. Please find our web site’s _Privacy Policy_ below.

* * *

Privacy Policy
==============

**Effective Date: This Privacy Policy was last revised on April 4, 2024.**

Thank you for visiting one of the websites of Sokolove Law, LLC and Sokolove Law, LLP. Our websites provide information about the legal services that we offer, provide general information and resources, and allow you to contact us.

All references to “Firm,” “we,” “us,” or “our” refer to Sokolove Law, LLC (which operates as a limited liability company in all states except California, Michigan, Tennessee and Virginia), Sokolove Law, LLP (which operates as a limited liability partnership in California, Michigan, Tennessee and Virginia), and their affiliated and related entities. All references to “websites” include Firm websites that post a link to this Privacy Policy, including this website, our other Firm-owned and/or operated websites that post this Privacy Policy, and websites that post this Privacy Policy that are operated for the Firm by service providers under agreement with the Firm.

This Privacy Policy governs your use of our websites. This Privacy Policy describes what information the Firm may collect about you on our websites, why we collect it, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may share it with third parties. This Privacy Policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. Unless otherwise indicated herein, this Privacy Policy does not apply to our data collection activities offline, and does not govern the data practices of third parties that may interact with our websites.

In addition, please review our [**Terms of Use**](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/terms/), which governs your use of the websites. **By using our websites, you consent to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use and our collection, use and sharing of your information and data, and other activities, as described below.** If you do not consent to our collecting and sharing your Personal Information (defined below) as described in this Privacy Policy, do not use the websites.

### 1\. What Information Do We Collect?

(A) **Information You Provide to Us**  
Personal Information and Demographic Information. We may ask you to provide us with certain categories of information, or you may otherwise provide us with information, through the websites such as: (1) personally identifiable information, which is information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally, such as your first and last name, e-mail address, home address and phone number (“Personal Information”); and (2) demographic information, such as information like your gender, your occupation or geographic information (“Demographic Information”). We may collect this information through various forms and in various places on the websites or Device (defined below), including, without limitation, the following places:

* consultation request forms, “contact us” forms, chat, text messages, or emails;
* account registration forms (if any); or
* survey participation interfaces or web blogs

Providing us with information about yourself is voluntary, but if you choose not to provide certain information you may not be able to take full advantage of all our websites’ features.

(B) **Information We Collect and Store as You Access and Use the Websites**   
In addition to any Personal Information, Demographic Information, or other information that you choose to submit to us, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) store or collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the websites (“Usage Information”). This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies that may be downloaded to your personal computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device (a “Device”) whenever you visit or interact with our websites. Privacy law concepts are evolving – it is possible that some Usage Information that we deem not to personally identify you and do not treat as Personal Information will nonetheless be deemed “personally identifiable information” by applicable law.

This Usage Information may include:

* your IP address, UDID or other unique device identifier (“Device Identifier”);
* whether a single user has accessed the websites using multiple Devices;
* your Device functionality (including browser, operating system, hardware, mobile network information, plug-ins);
* the URL that referred you to our websites, your website browsing history, and the areas within our websites that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you and your preferences;
* your Device location and characteristics; and
* certain other Device data, including time zone and the time of day

We may use various methods and technologies to store or collect Usage Information (“Tracking Technologies”). Tracking Technologies may set, change, alter or modify settings or configurations on your Device. A few of the Tracking Technologies include, without limitation, the following (and subsequent technology and methods later developed):

* **_Cookies_**. A cookie is a data file placed on a Device when it is used to visit the websites. A Flash cookie (or locally shared object) is a data file placed on a Device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built-in to or downloaded by you to your Device. HTML5 cookies are similar to Flash cookies but do not require a plug-in. Regular cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools that are available as part of most commercial browsers, and in some but not all instances can be blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Each browser you use will need to be set separately and different browsers offer different functionality and options in this regard. Also, these tools may not be effective with regard to Flash cookies or HTML5 cookies. For information on disabling Flash cookies go to [**adobe.com**](http://www.adobe.com/). Please be aware that if you disable or remove any cookies on your Device, some parts of our websites may not function properly, and that when you revisit our websites your ability to limit cookies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.
* **_Web Beacons_**. Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “web beacons”, “1×1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in our websites’ pages and messages. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the websites, to monitor how users navigate the websites, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.
* **_Embedded Scripts_**. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the websites, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to our websites, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.
* **_ETag, or entity tag_**. An ETag is a type of identifier assigned by a web server to a specific version of a resource found at a URL. If the resource content at that URL ever changes, a new and different ETag is assigned. Used in this manner ETags are similar to fingerprints, and they can be quickly compared to determine if two versions of a resource are the same or not. ETag tracking may generate unique tracking values even where the consumer blocks HTTP, Flash and/or HTML5 cookies.

We may use Tracking Technologies for a variety of purposes, including:

* **_Strictly Necessary_**. We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that we consider are strictly necessary to allow you to use and access our websites, including cookies required to prevent fraudulent activity, improve security or allow you to make use of certain functionality on our websites.
* **_Performance-Related_**. We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that are useful in order to assess the performance of the websites, including as part of our analytic practices or otherwise to improve the content, products or services offered through the websites.
* **_Functionality-Related_**. We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that are required to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing the websites, including identifying you when you signin to our websites or keeping track of our specified preferences, including in terms of the presentation of content on our websites.
* **_Targeting-Related_**. We may use Tracking Technologies to deliver content relevant to your interests on our websites based upon how you interact with our content. This includes using Tracking Technologies to understand the usefulness to you of the content that has been delivered to you.

There may be other Tracking Technologies now and later devised and used by us in connection with the websites.

(C) **Interactions with Third-Party Sites**   
The websites may include functionality that allows certain kinds of interactions between the websites and your account on a third-party site or application. The use of this functionality may involve the third-party operator providing certain information, including Personal Information, to us. If we offer and you choose to use this functionality to access our websites, the third-party site or application may send Personal Information about you to us.

### 2\. How Do We Use Your Information?

We may use your Personal Information (this includes your e-mail address, mailing address and telephone number), Demographic Information or Usage Information that is subject to this Privacy Policy for various purposes, including, but not limited to:

* to evaluate whether to represent you (and it may be shared with other law firms for this purpose) and to provide you with legal services if you are or become a client of the Firm
* to process transactions or provide you with information such as to send you electronic newsletters, or to provide you with special offers or promotional and marketing materials on behalf of us or third parties, including to let you know about new products, services or upcoming events;
* to enable you to participate in a variety of the websites’ features and to process your registration with the websites, including verifying your information is active and valid;
* to improve the websites, our marketing endeavors or our service offerings, and to customize your experience on the websites (such as serve you specific content that is relevant to you);
* to provide customer support and to contact you with regard to your use of the websites and, in our discretion, changes to the websites and/or websites’ policies;
* for our business purposes and the business purposes of third parties we share your information with;
* to communicate with you through short code or other text messaging, subject to our [SMS terms](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/sms-terms/);
* to contact you via phone, Device, email or hard-copy mail with information about our service offerings; and
* for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Please note that information submitted to the websites via a “contact us” or other similar function may not receive a response.

### 3\. How and When Do We Share Information With Third Parties?

We may from time to time elect to share certain information about you collected by us on the websites, including Personal Information, with third parties subject to the limits in this Privacy Policy and our [**Terms of Use**](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/terms/), including our [SMS terms](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/sms-terms/). For example, we may share information with our corporate affiliates for their everyday business purposes, to provide services or to perform marketing for us. We may share information with third parties who help us develop and promote products and services for us,  or to help us customize advertisements, offers, or other communications to you. If you are a California resident, you have the right to request additional information about this sharing as described below. We may share your Device Identifiers with third parties along with data related to you and your activities. In addition, we may share the information we have collected about you, including Personal Information, as disclosed at the time you provide your information and as described below or otherwise in this Privacy Policy. We also may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregated user statistics, with third parties.

By way of examples, the Firm may disclose your information as follows:

1. Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf. We may use third-party vendors to perform certain services on behalf of us or some or all of the websites, such as: (a) manage a database of client information; (b) hosting the websites; (c) designing and/or operating the websites’ features; (d) tracking the websites’ activities and analytics; (e) enabling us to send you information about our services or perform customer, marketing or other administrative services; and (f) other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. We may provide some of these vendors with access to user information, including Device Identifiers and Personal Information, to carry out the services they are performing for you or for us. Third-party analytics and other service providers for some of our websites may set and access their own Tracking Technologies on your Device and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, potentially including Personal Information, about you. We are not responsible for those third party technologies or activities arising out of them. However, some may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, and information we have been informed of regarding such choices for vendors and providers that we use on some or all of our websites from time to time is in an opt-out list available [**here**](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/third-party-systems/). We are not responsible for the completeness of the opt-out list or the effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties’ opt-out options.
2. To Protect the Rights of the Firm and our Users. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we may also disclose your information if we believe in our sole and absolute discretion that doing so is necessary or appropriate to: (i) protect or defend the rights, safety or property (such as collecting debts) of the Firm or third parties (including through the enforcement of this Privacy Policy, our [**Terms of Use**](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/terms/), and other applicable agreements and policies); or (ii) comply with legal and regulatory obligations (e.g., pursuant to law enforcement inquiries, subpoenas or court orders). To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we have complete discretion in electing to make or not make such disclosures, and to contest or not contest requests for such disclosures.
3. Affiliates and Business Transfer. We may share your information, including your Device Identifiers and Personal Information, Demographic Information and Usage Information with our subsidiaries, affiliates co-counsel, business partners, and related entities, subject to the limits of this Privacy Policy and our [**Terms of Use**](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/terms/). We also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all such information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the websites or applicable database; or (ii) in connection with a merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our interests and/or assets or other corporate change, including, during the course of any due diligence process.

### 4\. What About Information I Disclose Publicly or to Others?

1. User Generated Content and Public Information. The websites may permit you to submit various types of content, including images, text and Personal Information (collectively, “User Generated Content”), such as on blogs and message boards. We or others may store, display, reproduce, publish, distribute or otherwise use User Generated Content online or offline in any media or format (currently existing or hereafter developed) and may or may not attribute it to you. Others may have access to this User Generated Content and may have the ability to share it with third parties. Please think carefully before deciding what information you share, including Personal Information, in connection with your User Generated Content. We are not responsible for the privacy or security of any information that you make publicly available on the websites or what others do with information you share with them on the websites.
2. Name and Likeness. We may also publish your name, voice, likeness and other Personal Information that is part of your User Generated Content, and we may use the content, or any portion of the content, for advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. For full terms and conditions regarding User Generated Content you submit to the websites, please review our Terms of Use.

### 5\. Do Third-Party Content and Links to Third-Party Sites Appear on the Websites?

The websites may contain content that is supplied by a third party, and those third parties may collect Usage Information and your Device Identifier when pages from the websites are served to you. In addition, when you are on the websites you may be directed to other services that are operated and controlled by third parties that we do not control. We are not responsible for the data collection and privacy practices employed by any of these third parties or their services and they may be tracking you across multiple sites and may be sharing the results of that tracking with us and/or others.

### 6\. How Do I Change My Information?

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided if you choose to contact us for a case evaluation. You may correct or update the Personal Information you have provided through the websites by contacting us at: 1-800-706-5358.

### 7\. What About Transfer of Information to the United States?

If you are from a non-U.S. country, please be aware that the Personal Information you submit, ‎‎including information provided through our websites, is being sent to a location in the ‎United States. ‎The data protection laws in the United States are likely different from those of the ‎country in ‎which you are located, and your Personal Information may be subject to access ‎requests from ‎governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of ‎the United ‎States. By providing such Personal Information through the websites, you are ‎consenting to (and ‎represent that you have authority to consent to), the transfer of such ‎information to the United ‎States for the uses and purposes described in this Privacy Policy. ‎Without limiting the above, for ‎the avoidance of doubt we do not have an establishment or target ‎‎people in the EEA or UK. ‎

### 8\. What Should Parents Know About Children?

We understand the importance of protecting children’s privacy in the interactive world. We do not use the websites to knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If you are a child under 13 years of age, you are not permitted to use the websites and should not send any information about yourself to us through the websites. In the event that we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from any child, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will dispose of that information in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and other applicable laws and regulations.

### 9\. How Do We Protect Personal Information You Provide to Us?

We make reasonable efforts to protect Personal Information that you submit over the websites from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, which may include the use of firewalls and other security measures on our servers. However, the Firm does not warrant or represent that its level of security meets or exceeds any particular standard, and no server or internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. You should take this into account when submitting Personal or confidential Information on any websites, including ours. Similarly, any information that you send us through the websites is not confidential or privileged, and may be subject to applicable disclosure and reporting requirements, as required by law.

### 10\. **Text Messaging Privacy Statement**

We strictly adhere to our [SMS Terms of Service](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/sms-terms/), which governs our use of your Personal Information for text messaging, including the use of short code or otherwise.

If you wish to opt-out of our SMS text messaging service, you may reply to our short code with the message “STOP” at any time. If you are experiencing issues with the messaging program you can reply with the keyword HELP for more assistance, or you can get help directly at [\[email protected\]](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or 866-444-9876.

### 11\. **Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, you have additional consumer privacy rights under California ‎law.  ‎For more information, review our California supplement here: [CCPA Privacy ‎Policy](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/california-privacy-policy/).

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents who have supplied personal information, as defined in the statute, to us, under certain circumstances, to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If this applies, you may obtain the categories of personal information shared and the names and addresses of all third parties that received personal information for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately prior calendar year (e.g. requests made in 2018 will receive information about 2019 sharing activities). To make such a request, please provide sufficient information for us to determine if this applies to you, attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California street address (not a post office box) for our response. To make such a request (limit one request per year), please send an e-mail to: [\[email protected\]](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), with “California Privacy Rights” as the subject line or mail us a letter to: Sokolove Law, LLC, 1330 Boylston St., Suite 400, Chestnut Hill, MA 02467, Attn: Legal Dept. You must include your full name, e-mail address, and street address in your request.

### 12\. **Social Security Protection Policy Statement**

It is our policy to protect the confidentiality of Social Security numbers (SSNs) from ‎misuse ‎and improper disclosure by maintaining and enforcing physical, ‎‎electronic, and procedural ‎‎safeguards. We prohibit unlawful disclosure of SSNs, and limit access to SSNs to our ‎personnel ‎who need access to SSNs in order to perform their job functions. We do not ‎disclose SSNs to ‎third parties except where required or ‎‎permitted by law.‎ ‎

### 13\. **What About Changes to This Privacy Policy?**

The Firm reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, change or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy and your use of our websites indicates your consent to the privacy policy posted at the time of use. To the extent any provision of this Privacy Policy is found by a competent tribunal to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed to the extent necessary for the remainder to be valid and enforceable.

### 14\. **How Can You Ask Questions or Raise Concerns?**

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy or practices described in it, you should contact us in the following ways:

* By Phone: 1-800-706-5358
* By Email: [\[email protected\]](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Start Your Free Case Review**

First Name\*

Last Name\*

Email Address\*

Phone Number\*

Diagnosis?\*\-Select Diagnosis-MesotheliomaAsbestosisLung CancerUndiagnosedOtherUnsure

Who Was Diagnosed?\*\-Select One-MyselfParentSpouseSiblingGrandparentFriendOther

Tell us your story (optional)

I understand by submitting this form that I am providing my consent to be contacted by Sokolove Law and its co-counsel, potentially using automated technology, at the number provided regarding my potential claim/their services. Consent is not required to use their services. Msg frequency varies, and message and data rates may apply. Reply HELP for help or STOP to unsubscribe. [SMS Terms of Service](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/sms-terms/). I understand and agree that by submitting this form I agree to the [Privacy Policy](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/privacy/) and [Terms of Use](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/terms/) and that this form does not create an attorney-client relationship and is not confidential or privileged and may be shared.

gclidintake sourcegasourcegamediumgacampaigngatermgacontentURLmatchtypenetworkmkwidcookieEntryPagecookieDeviceTypecookieOScookieScreenResolutioncookieBrowsercookieBrowserSizecookieReferrercookieLastClickEventcookieUserPathcookieLastUserPathcookieUserTimeZone

Submit Form

Secure Submission

[

](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/ "Sokolove Law")

1330 Boylston Street, Suite 400  
Chestnut Hill, MA 02467

For legal help, call [(800) 995-1212](tel:+18009951212 "For legal help, click to call")

Sokolove Law has helped thousands of people over the last 45 years get the legal attention they deserve. While filing a legal claim may seem overwhelming, our lawyers can help you every step of the way. [Contact us](https://www.sokolovelaw.com/about-us/contact-us/ "Connect With Us") by phone, use our online chat, or fill out our form today.

For legal help, call [(800) 995-1212](tel:+18009951212 "For legal help, click to call")

We have locations **nationwide** to serve you today.

**Sokolove Law - Tucson, AZ**2573 North 1st Avenue,  
Tucson, AZ 85719

**Sokolove Law - Phoenix, AZ**3737 North 7th Street, Suite 106,  
Phoenix, AZ 85014

**Sokolove Law - San Francisco, CA**455 Market Street, Suite 1270,  
San Francisco, CA 94105

**Sokolove Law - Farmington, CT**231 Farmington Avenue,  
Farmington, CT 06032

**Sokolove Law - Georgetown, DE**113 South Race Street,  
Georgetown, DE 19947

**Sokolove Law - Destin, FL**35008 Emerald Coast Parkway, Suite 301,  
Destin, FL 32541

**Sokolove Law - Maitland, FL**341 North Maitland Avenue, Suite 115  
Maitland, FL 32751

**Sokolove Law - Atlanta, GA**10 Glenlake Parkway Northeast, Suite 130,  
Atlanta, GA 30328

**Sokolove Law - Dubuque, IA**1635 Associates Drive, Suite 102,  
Dubuque, IA 52002

**Sokolove Law - Sugar City, ID**1908 North 2190 East,  
Sugar City, ID 83448

**Sokolove Law - Alton, IL**One Court Street,  
Alton, IL 62002

**Sokolove Law - Chicago, IL**47 West Polk Street, Suite 311,  
Chicago, IL 60605

**Sokolove Law - Indianapolis, IN**110 North Delaware Street,  
Indianapolis, IN 46204

**Sokolove Law - Overland Park, KS**9270 Glenwood Street, Suite C,  
Overland Park, KS 66212

**Sokolove Law - Wichita, KS**218 North Mosley Street,  
Wichita, KS 67202

**Sokolove Law - Erlanger, KY**102 Country Road,  
Erlanger, KY 41018

**Sokolove Law - Gonzales, LA**214 South Burnside Avenue, Suite 104,  
Gonzales, LA 70737

**Sokolove Law - Boston, MA**44 School Street, Suite 400,  
Boston, MA 02108

**Sokolove Law - Chestnut Hill, MA**1330 Boylston Street, Suite 400,  
Chestnut Hill, MA 02467

**Sokolove Law - Minneapolis, MN**250 Marquette Avenue, Suite 1380,  
Minneapolis, MN 55401

**Sokolove Law - Clayton, MO**225 South Meramec Avenue, Suite 411,  
Clayton, MO 63105

**Sokolove Law - Gulfport, MS**2601 14th Street,  
Gulfport, MS 39501

**Sokolove Law - Missoula, MT**317 East Spruce Street,  
Missoula, MT 59802

**Sokolove Law - Wilmington, NC**321 North Front Street, Suite 4,  
Wilmington, NC 28401

**Sokolove Law - Grand Forks, ND**217 South 4th Street,  
Grand Forks, ND 58201

**Sokolove Law - Eatontown, NJ**12 Christopher Way, Suite 200,  
Eatontown, NJ 07724

**Sokolove Law - Henderson, NV**2580 St. Rose Parkway, Suite 330,  
Henderson, NV 89074

**Sokolove Law - New York, NY**295 Madison Avenue, 22nd Floor,  
New York, NY 10017

**Sokolove Law - Beachwood, OH**25285 Penshurst Drive,  
Beachwood, OH 44122

**Sokolove Law - Edmond, OK**423 North Bryant Avenue,  
Edmond, OK 73034

**Sokolove Law - Conshohocken, PA**161 Washington Street, Suite 940,  
Conshohocken, PA 19428

**Sokolove Law - Smithfield, RI**265 George Washington Highway,  
Smithfield, RI 02917

**Sokolove Law - Greenville, SC**1007 East Washington Street,  
Greenville, SC 29601

**Sokolove Law - Houston, TX**403 Heights Boulevard,  
Houston, TX 77007

**Sokolove Law - Essex Junction, VT**15 Brickyard Road, Suite 2,  
Essex Junction, VT 05452

**Sokolove Law - Seattle, WA**4549 West Laurel Drive NE,  
Seattle, WA 98105

View All Sokolove Law Locations

While Sokolove Law LLC maintains joint responsibility, most cases are referred to other attorneys for principal responsibility. Do not stop taking a prescribed medication without first consulting with your doctor. Discontinuing a prescribed medication without your doctor's advice can result in injury or death. Copyright © 2003-2024 Sokolove Law, LLC. Sokolove Law and the Sokolove Law logo are federally registered trademarks of Sokolove Law, LLC.

Click here for live chatX

Hello, we're sorry to barge in, but we are available to answer your questions.

Would you like to speak to a live person?

No Yes
